Guide to the National Law Center records, 1865-2005 RG0014
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Law alumni photographs, 1921-1989; RG0014 Series 13; 7.5 Linear feet (Box 9, Box 8, Box 7, Box 6, Box 13, Box 12, Box 11, Box 10, Box 15, Box 14, Box 1, Box 2, Box 3, Box 4, Box 5)
  - Olber, undated (Box 8, Folder 127.98)
    Folder labeled 127 I, item #9
  - A man, undated (Box 8, Folder 127.99)
    Folder labeled 127 I, item #10
  - Negatives of prints of folder 127 I, undated (Box 8, Folder 127.1)
    Folder labeled 127 I, item #11
  - Paul K. Edgar and another man chatting, undated (Box 8, Folder 127.101)
    Folder labeled 127 J, item #1
  - Participants with refreshments, undated (Box 8, Folder 127.102)
    Folder labeled 127 J, item #2
  - Participants at a meeting, undated (Box 8, Folder 127.103)
    Folder labeled 127 J, item #3
  - Participants at a meeting, undated (Box 8, Folder 127.104)
    Folder labeled 127 J, item #4
  - An office View, undated (Box 8, Folder 127.105)
    Folder labeled 127 J, item #5
  - Participants of a meeting, undated (Box 8, Folder 127.106)
    Folder labeled 127 J, item #6
  - Negatives for prints of folder 127 J, undated (Box 8, Folder 127.107)
    Folder labeled 127 J, item #7
  - Negatives for prints of folder 127 J, undated (Box 8, Folder 127.108)
    Folder labeled 127 J, item #8
  - Negatives of groups and individuals, undated (Box 8, Folder 128.1)
    Folder labeled 128 A
  - Negatives of groups and individuals, undated (Box 8, Folder 128.2)
  - Negatives of groups and individuals, undated (Box 8, Folder 128.3)
  - Negatives of groups and individuals, undated (Box 8, Folder 128.4)
  - Negatives of groups and individuals, undated (Box 8, Folder 128.5)
  - Negatives of groups and individuals, undated (Box 8, Folder 128.6)
  - Negatives of groups and individuals, undated (Box 8, Folder 128.7)
  - Negatives of groups and individuals, undated (Box 8, Folder 128.8)
  - A reception scene, undated (Box 8, Folder 128.9)
    A participants having a refreshment, Folder labeled 128 B, item #1
  - A man in an office, undated (Box 8, Folder 128.1)
    Folder labeled 128 B, item #2
  - An audience, undated (Box 8, Folder 128.11)
    Folder labeled 128 B, item #3
  - A reception scene, undated (Box 8, Folder 128.12)
    A participants having a refreshment, Folder labeled 128 B, item #4
  - Negatives for prints of folder 128 B, undated (Box 8, Folder 128.13)
    Folder labeled 128 B, item #5
  - Two participants dining, undated (Box 8, Folder 128.14)
  - Participants dining, undated (Box 8, Folder 128.15)
    Folder labeled 128 B, item #6
  - Participants dining, undated (Box 8, Folder 128.16)
    Folder labeled 128 B, item #7
  - Participants dining, undated (Box 8, Folder 128.17)
    Folder labeled 128 B, item #8
  - Pres. Trachtenberg and other participants, undated (Box 8, Folder 128.18)
    Folder labeled 128 B, item #9
  - Groups at an entrance of a building, undated (Box 8, Folder 128.19)
    Folder labeled 128 B, item #10
  - Two participants shaking hands, undated (Box 8, Folder 128.2)
    Folder labeled 128 B, item #11
  - Two students, undated (Box 8, Folder 128.21)
    Folder labeled 128 B, item #12
  - Participants with refreshments, undated (Box 8, Folder 128.22)
    Folder labeled 128 B, item #13
  - Participants with refreshments, undated (Box 8, Folder 128.23)
    Folder labeled 128 B, item #14
  - Three students in front of a building, undated (Box 8, Folder 128.24)
    Folder labeled 128 B, item #15
  - Studetns in front of a building, undated (Box 8, Folder 128.25)
    Folder labeled 128 B, item #16
  - An audience, undated (Box 8, Folder 128.26)
    Folder labeled 128 B, item #17
  - Participants chatting, undated (Box 8, Folder 128.27)
    Folder labeled 128 B, item #18
  - A man and a women participating, undated (Box 8, Folder 128.28)
    Folder labeled 128 B, item #19
  - A man and two women chatting on a balcony building, undated (Box 8, Folder 128.29)
    Folder labeled 128 B, item #90
  - Participants with an honored individual, undated (Box 8, Folder 128.3)
    Folder labeled 128 B, item #21
  - Springs, Colorado, undated (Box 8, Folder 129.1)
  - Man talking, undated (Box 8, Folder 129.2)
  - People at refreshment table, undated (Box 8, Folder 129.3)
  - 2 Men, undated (Box 8, Folder 129.4)
  - 2 men and 1 woman, undated (Box 8, Folder 129.5)
  - Group of men and women, undated (Box 8, Folder 129.6)
  - Group of men and women, undated (Box 8, Folder 129.7)
  - Group of men and women, undated (Box 8, Folder 129.8)
  - Group of men and women, undated (Box 8, Folder 129.9)
  - Group of men and women(door labelled Carlton Rm), undated (Box 8, Folder 129.1)
  - Group of men and women, undated (Box 8, Folder 129.11)
  - Group of men and women, undated (Box 8, Folder 129.12)
  - Group of men and women, undated (Box 8, Folder 129.13)
  - 2 men and a woman, undated (Box 8, Folder 129.14)
  - Women and man entering Carlton Room, undated (Box 8, Folder 129.15)
  - Men and women, undated (Box 8, Folder 129.16)
  - 3 men and a woman, undated (Box 8, Folder 129.17)
  - Man and a woman, undated (Box 8, Folder 129.18)
  - Men and women in Carlton room, undated (Box 8, Folder 129.19)
  - Men and women in Carlton room, undated (Box 8, Folder 129.2)
  - Men and women, undated (Box 8, Folder 129.21)
  - Alice White, undated (Box 8, Folder 129.22)
  - Men and women in Carlton room, undated (Box 8, Folder 129.23)
  - 2 Men shaking hands at podium seen in item #1, undated (Box 8, Folder 129.24)
  - Men at podium (as in #1 and 24), undated (Box 8, Folder 129.25)
  - Sheet of Negatives- groups and individuals, undated (Box 8, Folder 129.26)
  - Cliff Dougherty with Colorado Alumni, undated (Box 8, Folder 130.1)
  - Group of men and women, undated (Box 8, Folder 130.2)
  - Man standing at bar counter, undated (Box 8, Folder 130.3)
  - Men and Women, undated (Box 8, Folder 130.4)
  - 2 Men, undated (Box 8, Folder 130.5)
  - Men and Women, undated (Box 8, Folder 130.6)
  - Men and women, with book titled The Cowboy, undated (Box 8, Folder 130.7)
  - 2 men and a women, undated (Box 8, Folder 130.8)
  - 3 Men, undated (Box 8, Folder 130.9)
  - group of men and women, undated (Box 8, Folder 130.1)
  - Men and Women, undated (Box 8, Folder 130.11)
  - 2 Women and a man, undated (Box 8, Folder 130.12)
  - 3 Men and a women, undated (Box 8, Folder 130.13)
  - Men and Women, undated (Box 8, Folder 130.14)
  - 2 Men, undated (Box 8, Folder 130.15)
  - Men and Women, undated (Box 8, Folder 130.16)
  - Women and man, undated (Box 8, Folder 130.17)
  - Men and women, undated (Box 8, Folder 130.18)
  - Men and Women, undated (Box 8, Folder 130.19)
  - 3 women, undated (Box 8, Folder 130.2)
  - Men and Women, undated (Box 8, Folder 130.21)
  - Men and women, undated (Box 8, Folder 130.22)
  - 2 Men, undated (Box 8, Folder 130.23)
  - Men and women, undated (Box 8, Folder 130.24)
  - Men and women, undated (Box 8, Folder 130.25)
  - Men and women, undated (Box 8, Folder 130.26)
  - Men and women, undated (Box 8, Folder 130.27)
  - Men and women, undated (Box 8, Folder 130.28)
  - Man and women, undated (Box 8, Folder 130.29)
  - Men and Women at indoor function(s), undated (Box 8, Folder 130.3)
  - Men and Women at indoor function(s), undated (Box 8, Folder 130.31)
  - Men and Women at indoor function(s), undated (Box 8, Folder 130.32)
  - 2 Women, undated (Box 8, Folder 130.33)
  - Man and Women, undated (Box 8, Folder 130.34)
  - Man and Women, undated (Box 8, Folder 130.35)
  - Men And Women, undated (Box 8, Folder 130.36)
  - Men and Women, undated (Box 8, Folder 130.37)
  - Men and Women, undated (Box 8, Folder 130.38)
  - Men and Women, undated (Box 8, Folder 130.39)
  - Men and Women, undated (Box 8, Folder 130.4)
  - Men and Women, undated (Box 8, Folder 130.41)
  - Men and Women, undated (Box 8, Folder 130.42)
  - Men and Women, undated (Box 8, Folder 130.43)
  - Men and Women, undated (Box 8, Folder 130.44)
  - Men and Women, undated (Box 8, Folder 130.45)
  - Men and Women, undated (Box 8, Folder 130.46)
  - Men and Women, undated (Box 8, Folder 130.47)
  - Men and Women, undated (Box 8, Folder 130.48)
  - Men and Woman, undated (Box 8, Folder 130.49)
  - Man And Women, undated (Box 8, Folder 130.5)
  - Sheet of Negatives Strips- Men and Women, undated (Box 8, Folder 130.51)
  - Sheet of Negatves Strips- Men and Women, undated (Box 8, Folder 130.52)
  - Building: Law School, undated (Box 8, Folder 131.1)
    Architectural Model, Unidentified
  - Building: Law School, undated (Box 8, Folder 131.2)
    Architectural Drawing, Unidentified
  - Building: Law School, undated (Box 8, Folder 131.3)
  - Ticket for slides, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 131.4)
  - Group, Men and Women standing and talking, undated (Box 8, Folder 132.1)
  - Group, Men and Women standing and talking, undated (Box 8, Folder 132.2)
  - Group, Men and Women standing and talking, undated (Box 8, Folder 132.3)
  - Group, Men and Women standing and talking, undated (Box 8, Folder 132.4)
  - Group, Men and Women standing and talking, undated (Box 8, Folder 132.5)
  - Dialogue between seated group facing classroom and class participants, undated (Box 8, Folder 132.6)
  - Men and women standing around talking, undated (Box 8, Folder 132.7)
  - Group of men and women, undated (Box 8, Folder 132.8)
    Man holding sign that says: Patton, Boggs + Blow, Unidentified
  - Group, Men and women socializing, undated (Box 8, Folder 132.9)
  - Identical picture of print number 6, but darker exposure, undated (Box 8, Folder 132.1)
  - Cheaking in for an event, undated (Box 8, Folder 132.11)
  - Cheaking in for an event, undated (Box 8, Folder 132.12)
  - Men and women by shedule of events, undated (Box 8, Folder 132.13)
  - Checking in for event, undated (Box 8, Folder 132.14)
  - National Press Club, undated (Box 8, Folder 133.1)
    Speaker, Unidentified
  - National Press Club, undated (Box 8, Folder 133.2)
    Men talking, Unidentified
  - National Press Club, undated (Box 8, Folder 133.3)
  - 2 Men, undated (Box 8, Folder 134.1)
  - 2 Men, undated (Box 8, Folder 134.2)
  - 3 Men, undated (Box 8, Folder 134.3)
  - 3 Men, undated (Box 8, Folder 134.4)
  - Men and women at function with refreshments, undated (Box 8, Folder 134.5)
  - Men and women at function, undated (Box 8, Folder 134.6)
  - Man and women talking holding beverages, undated (Box 8, Folder 134.7)
  - Men and women with beverages- they have name tags from other universities, undated (Box 8, Folder 134.8)
  - 2 Men, undated (Box 8, Folder 134.9)
  - Men with beverages, talking, wearing name tags from other universities, undated (Box 8, Folder 134.1)
  - Men and women at same function as above, undated (Box 8, Folder 134.11)
  - Women and man at same function, undated (Box 8, Folder 134.12)
  - Women and man at same function, undated (Box 8, Folder 134.13)
  - 2 Men, undated (Box 8, Folder 134.14)
  - Man and Women in a classroom, undated (Box 8, Folder 134.15)
    Unidentified, print has been marked over with black lines
  - People at same function, undated (Box 8, Folder 134.16)
  - Women and men at function, undated (Box 8, Folder 134.17)
  - Men at same function, undated (Box 8, Folder 134.18)
  - Men and woman, undated (Box 8, Folder 134.19)
  - 2 Men, undated (Box 8, Folder 134.2)
  - 2 Men, undated (Box 8, Folder 134.21)
  - 2 Men, undated (Box 8, Folder 134.22)
  - 7 stripes of Negatives, undated (Box 8, Folder 134.23)
  - 4 stripes of Negatives, undated (Box 8, Folder 134.24)
  - People on panal, undated (Box 8, Folder 135.1)
    1 name is clear Theodore Levine, Very dark
  - Men and women on panal, undated (Box 8, Folder 135.2)
    Alexia Morrison, Ira Sorkin, Theodore Levine, dark
  - Panal and spectators, undated (Box 8, Folder 135.3)
    Dark
  - Men and women on panal and spectators, undated (Box 8, Folder 135.4)
  - Women and men on panal, undated (Box 8, Folder 135.5)
  - Class, undated (Box 8, Folder 135.6)
  - Men on panal, undated (Box 8, Folder 135.7)
    Theodore Levine and Edward Herling, dark
  - Men and women on panal, undated (Box 8, Folder 135.8)
  - Men and women on panal, undated (Box 8, Folder 135.9)
  - Men and women on panal and spectators, undated (Box 8, Folder 135.1)
  - Women and men, undated (Box 8, Folder 135.11)
  - Men in hallway, talking by lockers, undated (Box 8, Folder 135.12)
  - Panal and spectators, undated (Box 8, Folder 135.13)
  - Sheet of 5 rows of negatives, undated (Box 8, Folder 135.14)
  - Law Alumni Association gathering, undated (Box 8, Folder 136.1)
    Unidentified, people seated at tables
  - Law Alumni Association gathering, undated (Box 8, Folder 136.2)
    Unidentified, receiving line
  - Law Alumni Association gathering, undated (Box 8, Folder 136.3)
    Unidentified, people at round tables watching something
  - Law Alumni Association gathering, undated (Box 8, Folder 136.4)
    Unidentified, people seated at round table talking
  - Law Alumni Association, undated (Box 8, Folder 136.5)
    Unidentified, Speaker at podium
  - Law Alumni Association, undated (Box 8, Folder 136.6)
  - Law Alumni Association, undated (Box 8, Folder 136.7)
  - Law Alumni Association, undated (Box 8, Folder 136.8)
  - Sheet of Negatives, undated (Box 8, Folder 136.9)
  - Sheet of Negatives, undated (Box 8, Folder 136.1)
  - Men wearing name tags, shaking hands, undated (Box 8, Folder 137.1)
  - Man at podium, Law Alumni Association, undated (Box 8, Folder 137.2)
  - Man listening to speaker, undated (Box 8, Folder 137.3)
  - Women and men talking, undated (Box 8, Folder 137.4)
  - Men and women talking, undated (Box 8, Folder 137.5)
  - Men and women, undated (Box 8, Folder 137.6)
  - Man at podium, undated (Box 8, Folder 137.7)
  - Men at table, including Professor Glenn Weston and Dean Friedenthal, undated (Box 8, Folder 137.8)
  - Man at podium, undated (Box 8, Folder 137.9)
  - Sheet of Negatives, undated (Box 8, Folder 137.1)
  - 200th Anniversary of patent law celebration, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 138.1)
    Hosted by IPD and professor Donald Banner, Gene Stockman
  - Men and women at gathering, undated (Box 8, Folder 138.2)
  - Men and women getting someting to drink, undated (Box 8, Folder 138.3)
  - James E. Denny, undated (Box 8, Folder 138.4)
  - Man at podium, undated (Box 8, Folder 138.5)
  - Men and women at gathering, undated (Box 8, Folder 138.6)
  - Men at gathering, undated (Box 8, Folder 138.7)
  - Men at gathering, undated (Box 8, Folder 138.8)
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion Class of 1939, NLC Faculty Lounge, 04/1989 (Box 8, Folder 139.1)
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion Class of 1939, NLC Faculty Lounge, 04/1989 (Box 8, Folder 139.2)
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion Class of 1939, NLC Faculty Lounge, 04/1989 (Box 8, Folder 139.3)
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion Class of 1939, NLC Faculty Lounge, 04/1989 (Box 8, Folder 139.4)
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion Class of 1939, NLC Faculty Lounge, 04/1989 (Box 8, Folder 139.5)
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion Class of 1939, NLC Faculty Lounge, 04/1989 (Box 8, Folder 139.6)
    G. Brown, Friedenthal, Gerald Gearty, G.B. Craighill
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion Class of 1939, NLC Faculty Lounge, 04/1989 (Box 8, Folder 139.7)
    G. Bowden, Craighill
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion Class of 1939, NLC Faculty Lounge, 04/1989 (Box 8, Folder 139.8)
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion Class of 1939, NLC Faculty Lounge, 04/1989 (Box 8, Folder 139.9)
    Garver
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion Class of 1939, NLC Faculty Lounge, 04/1989 (Box 8, Folder 139.1)
    G. Gearty
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion Class of 1939, NLC Faculty Lounge, 04/1989 (Box 8, Folder 139.11)
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion Class of 1939, NLC Faculty Lounge, 04/1989 (Box 8, Folder 139.12)
    George R. Brown
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion Class of 1939, NLC Faculty Lounge, 04/1989 (Box 8, Folder 139.13)
    Gearty
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion Class of 1939, NLC Faculty Lounge, 04/1989 (Box 8, Folder 139.14)
    D. Garver
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion Class of 1939, NLC Faculty Lounge, 04/1989 (Box 8, Folder 139.15)
    G.R. Brown
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion Class of 1939, NLC Faculty Lounge, 04/1989 (Box 8, Folder 139.16)
    Paris
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion Class of 1939, NLC Faculty Lounge, 04/1989 (Box 8, Folder 139.17)
    W. Weisburger
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion Class of 1939, NLC Faculty Lounge, 04/1989 (Box 8, Folder 139.18)
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion Class of 1939, NLC Faculty Lounge, 04/1989 (Box 8, Folder 139.19)
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion Class of 1939, NLC Faculty Lounge, 04/1989 (Box 8, Folder 139.2)
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion Class of 1939, NLC Faculty Lounge, 04/1989 (Box 8, Folder 139.21)
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion Class of 1939, NLC Faculty Lounge, 04/1989 (Box 8, Folder 139.22)
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion Class of 1939, NLC Faculty Lounge, 04/1989 (Box 8, Folder 139.23)
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion Class of 1939, NLC Faculty Lounge, 04/1989 (Box 8, Folder 139.24)
    Dean Jenkins, Mrs. Paris
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion Class of 1939, NLC Faculty Lounge, 04/1989 (Box 8, Folder 139.25)
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion Class of 1939, NLC Faculty Lounge, 04/1989 (Box 8, Folder 139.26)
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion Class of 1939, NLC Faculty Lounge, 04/1989 (Box 8, Folder 139.27)
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion Class of 1939, NLC Faculty Lounge, 04/1989 (Box 8, Folder 139.28)
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion Class of 1939, NLC Faculty Lounge, 04/1989 (Box 8, Folder 139.29)
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion Class of 1939, NLC Faculty Lounge, 04/1989 (Box 8, Folder 139.3)
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion Class of 1939, NLC Faculty Lounge, 04/1989 (Box 8, Folder 139.31)
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion Class of 1939, NLC Faculty Lounge, 04/1989 (Box 8, Folder 139.32)
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion Class of 1939, NLC Faculty Lounge, 04/1989 (Box 8, Folder 139.33)
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion Class of 1939, NLC Faculty Lounge, 04/1989 (Box 8, Folder 139.34)
    Class of 1939 Reunion Group Picture
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion Class of 1939, NLC Faculty Lounge, 04/1989 (Box 8, Folder 139.35)
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion Class of 1939, NLC Faculty Lounge, 04/1989 (Box 8, Folder 139.36)
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion Class of 1939, NLC Faculty Lounge, 04/1989 (Box 8, Folder 173.38)
    Dean Kramer, Frank Parks, missing
  - Three men, undated (Box 9, Folder 140.1)
  - unidentified, undated (Box 9, Folder 140.2)
  - Group photo, undated (Box 9, Folder 140.3)
    A woman and two men, unidentified
  - Group photo, undated (Box 9, Folder 140.4)
  - Group photo, undated (Box 9, Folder 140.5)
  - Group photo, undated (Box 9, Folder 140.6)
  - Group photo, undated (Box 9, Folder 140.7)
  - Group photo, undated (Box 9, Folder 140.8)
  - Sheet of negatives, undated (Box 9, Folder 140.9)
  - Sheet of negatives, undated (Box 9, Folder 140.1)
  - 2 Men and a woman at long dining table, undated (Box 9, Folder 141.1)
  - Scenic View, undated (Box 9, Folder 141.2)
  - Man and woman toasting each other, undated (Box 9, Folder 141.3)
  - Men and women, undated (Box 9, Folder 141.4)
  - Men and women, undated (Box 9, Folder 141.5)
  - Mary Roulebush and Marshall Snider, undated (Box 9, Folder 141.6)
  - Men and women, undated (Box 9, Folder 141.7)
  - Men and women, undated (Box 9, Folder 141.8)
  - GW Law Alumni Breakfast, undated (Box 9, Folder 141.9)
  - GW Law Alumni Breakfast featuring Dean Friedenthal, undated (Box 9, Folder 141.1)
  - Susan Medalie and Dean Friedenthal, undated (Box 9, Folder 141.11)
  - 2 Men, undated (Box 9, Folder 141.12)
    Picture very dark
  - Dean Jenkins, Sheldon Cohen, Dean Friedenthal, undated (Box 9, Folder 141.13)
  - 2 Men, undated (Box 9, Folder 141.14)
  - 2 Men and a woman, undated (Box 9, Folder 141.15)
  - 2 Men, undated (Box 9, Folder 141.16)
  - 2 Men, undated (Box 9, Folder 141.17)
  - 2 Men at scenic overlook, undated (Box 9, Folder 141.18)
  - 2 Men, undated (Box 9, Folder 141.19)
  - 2 Men at scenic overlook (Joe Brand, Dean Frieden), undated (Box 9, Folder 141.2)
  - 1 Man, undated (Box 9, Folder 141.21)
  - 2 Men, undated (Box 9, Folder 141.22)
  - 1 Woman and 2 Men, undated (Box 9, Folder 141.23)
  - Sheet of Negatives, undated (Box 9, Folder 141.24)
  - Sheet of Negatives, undated (Box 9, Folder 141.25)
  - Men and women talking at social gathering, undated (Box 9, Folder 142.1)
    Partial exposure
  - Pres. Trachtenberg and a man, undated (Box 9, Folder 142.2)
  - Man and woman at gathering, undated (Box 9, Folder 142.3)
  - Judge Harold Greene and woman at gathering, undated (Box 9, Folder 142.4)
    Partial exposure, another cropped version of photo with the same item number
  - 2 Men at gathering, undated (Box 9, Folder 142.5)
  - People at gathering, undated (Box 9, Folder 142.6)
  - People dancing, undated (Box 9, Folder 142.7)
  - Men and women, undated (Box 9, Folder 142.8)
  - Dennis O'Rowke and Chapman, undated (Box 9, Folder 142.9)
  - speaker, undated (Box 9, Folder 142.1)
  - standing speaker, undated (Box 9, Folder 142.11)
  - Woman speaking with judge, undated (Box 9, Folder 142.12)
  - Woman and Wayne Arden, undated (Box 9, Folder 142.13)
  - Woman and 2 men (one is Russell Hens), undated (Box 9, Folder 142.14)
  - Men and Women, undated (Box 9, Folder 142.15)
    Partial exposure and blurry
  - Men, undated (Box 9, Folder 142.16)
  - Men and Women, undated (Box 9, Folder 142.17)
  - Sheet of Negatives, undated (Box 9, Folder 142.18)
  - Two men, undated (Box 9, Folder 143.1)
  - Two women and a man, undated (Box 9, Folder 143.2)
  - Bruce G. Campbell, undated (Box 9, Folder 143.3)
  - Two men and a woman, undated (Box 9, Folder 143.4)
  - A man and a woman, undated (Box 9, Folder 143.5)
  - Two men, undated (Box 9, Folder 143.6)
  - Two men, undated (Box 9, Folder 143.7)
  - Two men and a woman, undated (Box 9, Folder 143.8)
  - Two men and a woman, undated (Box 9, Folder 143.9)
  - Two men and two women, undated (Box 9, Folder 143.1)
  - A man and a woman, undated (Box 9, Folder 143.11)
  - Two women and a man, undated (Box 9, Folder 143.12)
  - A man, undated (Box 9, Folder 143.13)
  - Three woman and four men, undated (Box 9, Folder 143.14)
  - Three women, undated (Box 9, Folder 143.15)
  - A man giving a presentaion, undated (Box 9, Folder 143.16)
  - Two men and two women, undated (Box 9, Folder 143.17)
  - Three men, undated (Box 9, Folder 143.18)
  - Two men, undated (Box 9, Folder 143.19)
  - A man and a woman, undated (Box 9, Folder 143.2)
  - Two men, undated (Box 9, Folder 143.21)
  - Two women and two men, undated (Box 9, Folder 143.22)
  - A group of people watching a presentaion, undated (Box 9, Folder 143.23)
  - Negatives of men and women at presentaion, undated (Box 9, Folder 143.24)
  - Negatives of men and women at presentaion, undated (Box 9, Folder 143.25)
  - Two men and a woman, undated (Box 9, Folder 144.1)
  - Three men and a woman, undated (Box 9, Folder 144.2)
  - Three men and a woman, undated (Box 9, Folder 144.3)
  - Four men posing for the camera, undated (Box 9, Folder 145.1)
  - A group of men and women posing for the camera, undated (Box 9, Folder 145.2)
  - Jacob Burns, Joe Brand and Van Vleck Moot Court, 04/1989 (Box 9, Folder 146.1)
    Student winners at the F. Street Club, unidentified
  - Jacob Burns, Joe Brand and Van Vleck Moot Court, 04/1989 (Box 9, Folder 146.2)
  - Jacob Burns, Joe Brand and Van Vleck Moot Court, 04/1989 (Box 9, Folder 146.3)
  - Jacob Burns, Joe Brand and Van Vleck Moot Court, 04/1989 (Box 9, Folder 146.4)
  - Jacob Burns, Joe Brand and Van Vleck Moot Court, 04/1989 (Box 9, Folder 146.5)
  - Jacob Burns, Joe Brand and Van Vleck Moot Court, 04/1989 (Box 9, Folder 146.6)
  - Jacob Burns, Joe Brand and Van Vleck Moot Court, 04/1989 (Box 9, Folder 146.7)
  - Jacob Burns, Joe Brand and Van Vleck Moot Court, 04/1989 (Box 9, Folder 146.8)
  - Jacob Burns, Joe Brand and Van Vleck Moot Court, 04/1989 (Box 9, Folder 146.9)